Irrespective of the
lawlessness that that
You hear them saying that
Ad-dunya naqdun
This world is cashed down
Worldly affairs is cashed
down
Once you do kidnapping they
give you
cash
And this is what the
kidnappers and
the banditry
This is what they spread,
be themselves on the social
media
May Allah protect all of us
The money is cash,
cashed down
Wal-akhiratu nasi'a
If you say you want to be
patient
Til akhirah
Observing Salat and avoiding
prohibitions
That one is foul
You only get down one liter,
liter is foul
Wal-naqdu anfa'u minal nasi'a
And what you get now,
now, now, now
It is more beneficial than
what you
are promised in the future
Fa ana la abi'u naqdan bi
nasi'a
I will not leave,
I will not transact something
That I can get now,
now, now
I will not leave it,
hoping to get it tomorrow
No, I want it now